(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-pro-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
聖なる夜
A holy night
4つの星が、ひとつになるとき
When four stars become one
奇跡が、はじまる。
A miracle begins.
さあ
Come on!
Hyper Jumpin'
飛び越えよう
Let's jump over
ハイになって
Get hyped
ハイになるまで
Until we're fully hyped
ダッシュしてきた
We dashed here
Hyper Jumpin'
海の向こうまでも
Even beyond the sea
届くの？
Will it reach?
近づきたいの
I want to get closer
ドキドキした
Did your heart pound?
ギリギリ
Just barely
360度、どこからも
360 degrees, from anywhere
もっともっと高く飛びたいの
I want to jump higher and higher
Hyper Jumpin' Now
ここにいる。
I am here.
手が触れそうなほど。
Close enough to touch.
Hyper Jumpin' Now
2025.12.21 Sun
みるライブから、会えるライブへ。
From a live you watch, to a live where you can meet.
ねぽらぼライブ参加方法
How to Participate in NePoLaBo Live
開催タイムスケジュール
Event Time Schedule
ねぽらぼ応援セット
NePoLaBo Cheering Set
デジタルグッズ
Digital Goods
ねぽらぼライブ記念Tシャツ
NePoLaBo Live Commemorative T-Shirt
ねぽらぼライブフォトコンテスト
NePoLaBo Live Photo Contest
聖なる夜
A holy night
4つの星が、ひとつになるとき
When four stars become one
奇跡が、はじまる。
A miracle begins.
さあ
Come on!
Hyper Jumpin'
飛び越えよう
Let's jump over
ハイになって
Get hyped
ハイになるまで
Until we're fully hyped
ダッシュしてきた
We dashed here
Hyper Jumpin'
海の向こうまでも
Even beyond the sea
届くの？
Will it reach?
近づきたいの
I want to get closer
ドキドキした
Did your heart pound?
ギリギリ
Just barely
360度、どこからも
360 degrees, from anywhere
もっともっと高く飛びたいの
I want to jump higher and higher
Hyper Jumpin' Now
ここにいる。
I am here.
手が触れそうなほど。
Close enough to touch.
Hyper Jumpin' Now
2025.12.21 Sun
みるライブから、会えるライブへ。
From a live you watch, to a live where you can meet.
参加方法：ホロアース (¥1,500) vs 動画配信 (¥3,500)
How to Join: Holoearth (¥1,500) vs Streaming (¥3,500)
ホロアースからの参加：IDカードホルダーを購入
Join via Holoearth: Purchase ID Card Holder
開催スケジュール：2025年12月21日(日) 19:00
Schedule: Dec 21, 2025 (Sun) 19:00
ねぽらぼ応援セット (グッズ＋IDカード)
NePoLaBo Support Set (Goods + ID Card)
デジタルグッズ (Tシャツ、マスコット、ペンライト)
Digital Goods (T-Shirt, Mascot, Penlight)
文字プレート・花火・特製エモート
Text Plates, Fireworks, Special Emotes
ねぽらぼライブ記念Tシャツ
NePoLaBo Live Commemorative T-Shirt
ねぽらぼライブ フォトコンテスト
NePoLaBo Live Photo Contest
聖なる夜
Holy Night
4つの星が、ひとつになるとき
When four stars become one,
奇跡が、はじまる。
a miracle begins.
さあ
Come on!
Hyper Jumpin' 飛び越えよう
Hyper Jumpin', let's jump over it!
ハイになって灰になるまで 出してきな
Get high, until we turn to ash, let it all out!
Hyper Jumpin' 海の向こうまでも
Hyper Jumpin', even beyond the sea,
もっともっと近づきたいの
I want to get closer and closer.
Wow oh oh...
ドキドキしたい gimme gimme gimme 愛
I want to be excited, gimme gimme gimme love!
Wow oh oh...
もっともっと高く飛びたいの
I want to jump higher and higher.
Hyper Jumpin' Now
ここにいる。
I am here.
手が触れそうなほど。
Close enough to touch.
Hyper Jumpin' Now
みるライブから、会えるライブへ。
From a live you watch, to a live where you meet.
聖なる夜
Holy night.
4つの星が、ひとつになるとき
When four stars become one,
奇跡が、はじまる。
a miracle begins.
Hyper Jumpin' 飛び越えよう
Hyper Jumpin', let's jump over it!
ハイになって 灰になるまで 出し切って
Get high, give it your all until you turn to ash!
Hyper Jumpin' 海の向こうまで
Hyper Jumpin', to beyond the sea!
もっと ぐっと 近づきたいの
I want to get much, much closer.
Woah-oh-oh woah-oh-oh
ドキドキした ギリギリギリまで
Heart pounding, until the very limit.
Woah-oh-oh woah-oh-oh
誰よりもっと 高く飛びたいの
I want to fly higher than anyone else.
Hyper Jumpin' now
ここにいる。手が触れそうなほど。
I am here. Close enough to touch.
Hyper Jumpin' now!
ねぽらぼライブ参加方法
NePoLaBo Live Participation Method
ホロアースからの参加
Participation from Holoearth
ホロアースライブ 開催タイムスケジュール
Holoearth Live Event Schedule
ねぽらぼ応援セット
NePoLaBo Cheering Set
デジタルグッズ (ホロアースのアイテム)
Digital Goods (Holoearth Items)
ねぽらぼライブ記念Tシャツ
NePoLaBo Live Commemorative T-Shirt
ねぽらぼライブ フォトコンテスト
NePoLaBo Live Photo Contest
聖なる夜
Holy night
4つの星が、ひとつになるとき
When four stars become one
奇跡が、はじまる。
A miracle begins.
さあ
Come on
Hyper Jumpin' 飛び越えよ
Hyper Jumpin' jump over it
ハイになって 灰になるまで どうしてきな
Get high, until we turn to ash, do whatever
Hyper Jumpin' 海の向こうまでも
Hyper Jumpin' even beyond the sea
もっと近づきたい
I want to get closer
No! Wo oh oh Wo oh oh
ドキドキしたい キミ キミ キミと
I want my heart to pound with you you you
Hi! Wo oh oh Wo oh oh
もっともっと 高く飛びたいの
I want to fly higher and higher
Hyper Jumpin' Now
桃鈴ねね 尾丸ポルカ
雪花ラミィ 獅白ぼたん
Momosuzu Nene, Omaru Polka
Yukihana Lamy, Shishiro Botan
みるライブから、会えるライブへ。
From a live you watch, to a live where you meet.
奇跡が、はじまる。
A miracle begins.
さあ
Come on!
Hyper Jumpin' 飛び越えよ
Hyper Jumpin', let's jump over it!
Highになって Highになるまで
Get High, until we become High,
Touchしてきな
Come and touch!
Hyper Jumpin' 海の向こうまでも
Hyper Jumpin', even beyond the sea,
届く
it will reach.
もっと近づきたいの
I want to get even closer.
Wo-o-o-o-o
ドキドキした
My heart pounded,
キミキミキミ...
for you, you, you...
360度、どこからも。
360 degrees, from anywhere.
Wo-o-o-o-o
まだまだもっと高く飛びたいの
I want to jump much, much higher.
Hyper Jumpin' now
ここにいる。
I am here.
手が触れそうなほど。
Close enough to touch.
Hyper Jumpin' now
2025.12.21 Sun
Sunday, December 21, 2025
会場 HOLOEARTH
Venue: HOLOEARTH
みるライブから、会えるライブへ。
From a live you watch, to a live where you can meet.
ねぽらぼライブ参加方法
[How to Participate in NePoLaBo Live]
ホロアースライブ 開催タイムスケジュール
[Holoearth Live Event Schedule]
ねぽらぼ応援セット
[NePoLaBo Cheering Set]
デジタルグッズ (ホロアースのアイテム)
[Digital Goods (Holoearth Items)]
デジタルグッズ (スタンプ・エモート)
[Digital Goods (Stamps & Emotes)]
ねぽらぼライブ記念Tシャツ
[NePoLaBo Live Commemorative T-Shirt]
ねぽらぼライブ フォトコンテスト
[NePoLaBo Live Photo Contest]
聖なる夜
On this Holy Night,
4つの星が、ひとつになるとき
when four stars become one,
奇跡が、はじまる。
a miracle begins.
さあ
Come on!
Hyper Jumpin' 飛び越えよ
Hyper Jumpin', let's jump over it!
Highになって Highになるまで
Get High, until we become High,
Touchしてきな
Come and touch!
Hyper Jumpin' 海の向こうまでも
Hyper Jumpin', even beyond the sea,
届く
it will reach.
もっと近づきたいの
I want to get even closer.
Wo-o-o-o-o
ドキドキした
My heart pounded,
キミキミキミ...
for you, you, you...
360度、どこからも。
360 degrees, from anywhere.
Wo-o-o-o-o
まだまだもっと高く飛びたいの
I want to jump much, much higher.
Hyper Jumpin' now
ここにいる。
I am here.
手が触れそうなほど。
Close enough to touch.
Hyper Jumpin' now
2025.12.21 Sun
Sunday, December 21, 2025
会場 HOLOEARTH
Venue: HOLOEARTH
みるライブから、会えるライブへ。
From a live you watch, to a live where you can meet.
ねぽらぼライブ参加方法：ホロアースから参加 / 動画配信サービスによる「視聴するライブ」
NePoLaBo Live Participation Methods: Participate via Holoearth / 'Watch Live' via streaming services
ホロアースライブ 開催タイムスケジュール
Holoearth Live Event Time Schedule
聖なる夜
Holy Night
４つの星が、ひとつになるとき
When four stars become one
奇跡が、はじまる。
A miracle begins.
さあ
Come on!
Hyper Jumpin' 飛び越えよう
Hyper Jumpin', let's jump over it!
Highになって灰になるまで 楽しんじゃってイイんじゃない？
Get High until we turn to ash... isn't it fine to just have fun?
Hyper Jumpin'
海の向こうまでも
Even across the sea,
もっともっと近く
I want to get closer
いきたいの
and closer!
Woh oh oh...
ドキドキした
My heart pounded,
キミ キミ キミに High
High for you, you, you!
360度 どこからも
360 degrees, from anywhere,
もっと高く飛びたいの
I want to fly even higher!
Hyper Jumpin' Now
みるライブから、会えるライブへ。
From a live you watch, to a live where you can meet.
ピンポンパンポーン
(Chime sounds)
みなさん、メリークリスマス！
Everyone, Merry Christmas!
本日は「ねぽらぼライブ re:VISION」にご来場いただき、ありがとうございます。
Thank you for coming to 'NePoLaBo Live re:VISION' today.
ライブ開始はこの後、19時からの予定となっていますので、今しばらくお待ちください。
The live is scheduled to start shortly at 19:00, so please wait a little longer.
本公演のチラ見せ部分は、動画のYouTubeへの投稿が可能です。
For this preview section of the concert, you are allowed to upload videos to YouTube.
が！しかし！
But! However!
他のSNSは、音声なしの30秒以内の動画の投稿をお願いします。
For other SNS platforms, please limit uploads to videos under 30 seconds with NO audio.
静止画のスクショや感想などは全編を通じて可能なので、いっぱい呟きお願いします。
Screenshots and sharing impressions are allowed throughout the entire event, so please tweet a lot!
禁止事項ですが、本公演のミラー配信…
Regarding prohibitions: Mirror streaming of this performance...
…並びに、音声ありのライブ本編動画の一部SNSへの投稿となっています。
...and uploading parts of the main live video with audio to SNS are prohibited.
あ、みんな！遊びに来る準備はできてるかな？
Ah, everyone! Are you ready to come play?
ねね、誤解？タキシード着てる人いるかな？
Nene, am I seeing things? Is there anyone wearing a tuxedo?
雪民さんたちがどんな姿で会いに来てくれるか楽しみ！
I'm looking forward to seeing what kind of appearance the Yukimin will come to meet us in!
ホロアースのライブだから、好きな服装でライブ見れるのもいいよね。
Since it's a Holoearth live, it's great that you can watch the live in your favorite clothes, right?
スクショも撮っていいみたいなので、いろんな角度からたくさん撮ってほしいです。
It seems you can take screenshots too, so I want you to take lots from various angles.
そう！普通のライブだと、動いて見て回ったりはできないもんね。
That's right! In a normal live, you can't move around and look, right?
ねねたちの最高の写真、期待してるぞー！
I'm expecting the best photos of us Nene & co.!
というわけで、ライブ開始までもうしばらくお待ちください。
So, please wait a little longer until the live starts.
一緒にライブ、盛り上がっていこー！
Let's get hyped for the live together!
Hyper Jumpin' Now
ねぽらぼライブ re:VISION
NePoLaBo Live re:VISION
始まるぞー！
It's starting!
Hyper Jumpin' Now
ちょっと早めのクリスマス！
A slightly early Christmas!
盛り上がって行くぞー！
Let's get hyped!
Hyper Jumpin' 飛び出そう
Hyper Jumpin' Let's jump out
Come on baby 輝いて
Come on baby, shine
Heart キュンって Pump It Up
Heart goes 'kyun' and Pump It Up
Hyper Jumpin' 夢の先までは
Hyper Jumpin' To the end of the dream
もっともっと刺激が欲しいの
I want more and more stimulation
Hyper Jumpin' Now
Hyper Jumpin'
子どもくらい はしゃぐ方がお徳でしょ
It's better to be as playful as a child, right?
Nenechi! Nenechi! Nenechi!
低気圧から這い上がっていくテンション
Tension rising from low pressure
Polka! Polka! Polka!
酔いながら打ち返しまくるメンション
Shooting back mentions while getting drunk
Lamy! Lamy! Lamy!
カートを乗りこなして進むミッション
Mission: Master the cart and move forward
Botan! Botan! Botan!
このままスピード加速して
Accelerating speed just like this
たどり着く先に 何があるんだろう
What will be there at the destination?
止まらない気持ちは助走つけて
Getting a running start with these unstoppable feelings
次元を超えて行こう
Let's cross dimensions
さぁ
Come on
Hyper Jumpin' 飛び跳ねよう
Hyper Jumpin' Let's jump around
ハイになって灰になるまでダンシング Shake it up
Get high and dance until we turn to ash, Shake it up
Hyper Jumpin' 空の向こうまで
Hyper Jumpin' To the other side of the sky
もっともっと 近づきたいの
I want to get closer and closer
ドキドキしたい Gimme Gimme Gimme Love
I want to get excited, Gimme Gimme Gimme Love
もっともっと高く飛びたいの
I want to fly higher and higher
Hyper Jumpin' Now
Hyper Jumpin'
360度楽しめてるかな？
Are you enjoying the 360-degree view?
Hyper Jumpin' Now
斜めから攻めて解決クエスチョン
Solving the question by attacking from an angle
Nenechi! Nenechi! Nenechi!
ネガティブを切り裂いてくれるチェンソー
A chainsaw that tears through negativity
Polka! Polka! Polka!
流れるコメントと掛け合いセッション
A session of interplay with the flowing comments
Lamy! Lamy! Lamy!
エイムを鍛えて狙い撃つフリックショット
Training aim and shooting with a Flick Shot
Shishiro! Shishiro! Shishiro!
DisはNo No 好きならMore More More
Dis is No No, if you like it, More More More
邪魔するノイズは撃ち消せ Bang Bang Bang
Shoot down the interfering noise, Bang Bang Bang
遊びたいだけ
I just want to play
アンチは無視して
Ignore the antis
笑い飛ばして
Laugh it off
蹴飛ばせ
Kick it away
Kick it!! Jump Around!!
このまま僕らは旅をして
We will journey on like this
たどり着く先に 何があるんだろう
What awaits us at the destination?
信じた未来とリンクして
Linking with the future we believe in
次元を超えて行こう さぁ
Let's cross dimensions, come on!
Hyper Jumpin'
未来の向こうまで
To beyond the future
もっともっと近づきたいの
I want to get closer and closer
Wow wow wow...
ドキドキしたい
I want to be excited
ギリギリギリアイ
Love on the edge
Wow wow wow...
もっともっと高く飛びたいの
I want to jump higher and higher
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
Hyper Jumpin' Now
バイバーイ！
Bye bye!
イェーイ！お疲れ！
Yeah! Good work!
良かった！
That was good!
みんな元気ー？
Is everyone doing well?
元気モリモリだよー！
We're full of energy!
というわけで、自己紹介いきましょう！
With that said, let's do self-introductions!
ねねから！ねねから！
From Nene! From Nene!
じゃあみんな、アイテムとかの準備いいですか？
Alright everyone, are you ready with your items?
順番に行きますからね、みんなアイテムの準備してください。
We'll go in order, so everyone please prepare your items.
ねぽらぼで行くからね。
We'll go in NePoLaBo order.
どれくらい待つ？この準備。
How long should we wait for this preparation?
ちょっと待ったほうがいいか。
Maybe we should wait a bit.
みんなショートカにペンライト入れといてね。
Everyone, put your penlights in your shortcuts.
1, 2, 3, 4 でこう出してね。
Bring them out on 1, 2, 3, 4.
5, 4, 3, 2, 1, はいどうぞ！
5, 4, 3, 2, 1, go ahead!
はい！じゃあみんな行くよ！
Okay! Here we go everyone!
ホロライブ5期生、ねぽらぼの「ね」！
Hololive 5th Gen, NePoLaBo's 'Ne'!
みんなの心のー…
Everyone's heart's...
せーの！
Ready, set!
エナジードリンク！！
Energy drink!!
桃鈴ねねです！
I'm Momosuzu Nene!
よろしくねー！
Nice to meet you!
じゃあ次！
Next!
はい！切り替えて！
Yes! Switching gears!
尾丸ポルカだよー！
It's Omaru Polka!
いつものないか？ポルカおるか？
Is the usual one not there? Is Polka here?
おるよ！
I'm here!
ねぽらぼの「ぽ」、尾丸ポルカです！
NePoLaBo's 'Po', I'm Omaru Polka!
よろちくー！
Nice to meet you!
こんらみー！
Kon-Lamy!
ホロライブ5期生の雪花ラミィです！
I'm Hololive 5th Gen's Yukihana Lamy!
ラミィちゃん好き？
Do you like Lamy-chan?
愛してる！！
I love you!!
大好きだよ！
I love you very much!
そして最後！
And lastly!
はい、みんな準備してる？
Yes, is everyone ready?
なんの準備？
Ready for what?
スタンプ？スタンプ？
Stamp? Stamp?
なんかあるっしょ。
There's something, right?
ららーいおん！ホロライブ5期生、獅白ぼたんです。
La-lion! Hololive 5th Gen, Shishiro Botan.
ガウガウいただきます！
Gau gau, I will partake!
いただきますよー！
She's going to eat!
みんなバッチリ決まったところで…
Now that everyone has posed perfectly...
新しい試み、「re:VISION」ライブということで。
With this new endeavor, the 're:VISION' live.
詳しいことは概要欄やホロアースの公式HPを確認してください。
Please check the description or Holoearth's website for details.
はい、ということで今日はでもみんながね、アバターで参加してるし…
Yes, so today, everyone is participating with avatars...
いろんな角度からのこの振り付け、確認して欲しいなと思います。
I want you to check out this choreography from various angles.
ねねの服着てる人はいると信じてるからねみんな！
I believe there are people wearing Nene's clothes!
いるかな？
Are they there?
もっとよく映して！
Show them more clearly!
いいよ！いいよ！
Good! Good!
みんなとやれることなんかない？尾丸。
Isn't there something we can do with everyone? Omaru.
え？何かな？何かないですかね？
Eh? What could it be? Is there nothing?
よし、あれやろうあれ。
Alright, let's do that thing.
走りましょう皆さん！
Let's run, everyone!
ここから走るよ！
We'll run from here!
ポルカが先頭で、こうグルっと走ってみよう。
With Polka in the lead, let's try running around like this.
じゃあみんなついてきてね。
Then everyone follow me.
せーので行くか。
Shall we go on 'se-no'?
じゃあせーの！わーーー！
Then, se-no! Waaaa!
先生！一人速いやつがいます！
Teacher! There's one fast guy!
あれ？あれ？ポルカ、ポルカ…
Huh? Huh? Polka, Polka...
早くしてください！
Please hurry up!
誰もついてこれないよ！
No one can keep up!
反対回り！
Run the other way!
先生！本気のやつがいます！
Teacher! There's someone going all out!
あれ？逆、逆！
Huh? Opposite, opposite!
あれ？遅れてる？
Huh? Am I late?
はい、ゴール！お疲れ様！
Yes, goal! Good work!
みんなと走れて楽しい！
It was fun running with everyone!
一緒に走れることなかなかないからね。
It's rare to be able to run together like this.
ちなみにですね、本番の曲の最中ですが…
By the way, during the actual songs...
周りの人がね、ジャンプする時とかも、見えやすいように配慮してください。
Please be considerate so people around you can see, even when jumping.
ジャンプ！ピピ！
Jump! Pipi!
周りの人に配慮して！
Be considerate of those around you!
盛り上がってるところ申し訳ないんですが…
I'm sorry to interrupt while we're having fun, but...
ここで悲しいお知らせがあります。
I have some sad news here.
え？何なに？
Eh? What what?
ということで皆さんすみません。YouTubeとホロアースのエントランスである…
So, everyone, I'm sorry. The free broadcast on YouTube and the Holoearth entrance...
フォーカルスクエアでの無料配信はここまでとなっております。
...at Focal Square ends here.
はい！引き続き...
Yes! Continuing on...
壊す？
Break it?
壊す... っぽい... 最後ではライブが配信されますので。
Break... ish... the rest of the live will be streamed at the end.
YouTubeで見てる方は、動画の概要欄をチェックしてください。
For those watching on YouTube, please check the video description.
はい。
Yes.
で、チケット持ってる方で、まだこっちに来てないフォーカルスクエアのみんなは...
And for everyone in the Focal Square who has a ticket but hasn't come here yet...
よかったらこっちに来てください。
Please come over here if you'd like.
来てください。
Please come!
えー、じゃあというわけで。
Well then, with that said.
はい！
Yes!
YouTubeのみんな...
Everyone on YouTube...
バイバ〜イ！
Bye-bye!
爽やかだな。
That was refreshing.
というわけで。
So then.
次からはソロ曲ですが。
We're moving on to the solo songs.
まずは誰からかな？
Who's going first?
誰かな、誰かな？
Who is it? Who is it?
誰かな、誰かな〜？
ねねちゃん！
Nene-chan!
は〜い！
Yesss!
それではよろしく！
Take it away!
みんなドンドン盛り上がって...
Everyone, let's get hyped up...
いくぞ〜！
...and keep it going!
お〜！
Ohhh!
無料パートは終了いたしました。ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The sneak peek part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching!